Register of the Alex N. Dragnich Papers, 1859-2008
Hoover Institution Archives
- Correspondence, 1916-1988 (Boxes 2-17)
  - Kirkpatrick, Evron, 1951-53, 1974 (Folder 54)
  - Kirkpatrick, Helen, 1951-52 (Folder 55)
  - Kirkpatrick, Jeane, 1985 (Folder 56)
  - Kissinger, Henry A., 1970-71 (Folder 57)
  - Knjizevni Vesnik, 1980 (Folder 58)
  - Knowledge Resources, Inc., 1980 (Folder 59)
  - Koch, Malcolm, 1974 (Folder 60)
  - Kogekar, Sadanand, 1957 (Folder 61)
  - Kohler, Walter, 1951 (Folder 62)
  - Kojadinovic, Momir, 1960 (Folder 63)
  - Kolaja, Jiri, 1963 (Folder 64)
  - Kolarek, Joseph, 1952-57 (Folder 65)
  - Kolb, William L., 1957 (Folder 66)
  - Komadinic, Slobodan, 1955 (Folder 67)
  - Korbel, Josef, 1955 (Folder 68)
  - Korry, Edward M., 1957-1982 (Folder 69)
  - Kostic, Milos, 1958, 1976 (Folder 70)
  - Kostich, George J., 1986 (Folder 71)
  - Kovacevich, Dan L., 1956 (Folder 72)
  - Krek, Michael, 1953-58 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Kressley, Kondrad, 1974-75 (Folder 2)
  - Kronick, Bernard, 1976 (Folder 3)
  - Kull, Irving S., 1946 (Folder 4)
  - Kypriotis, Mary, 1961-62 (Folder 5)
  - Lambert, W. C. B., 1956 (Folder 6)
  - Lampe, John R., 1974 (Folder 7)
  - Lane, Arthur Bliss, 1953 (Folder 8)
  - LaPalombara, Joseph, 1959 (Folder 9)
  - Larson, D. R., 1953 (Folder 10)
  - Larson, Thomas B., 1958 (Folder 11)
  - Lausche, Frank, 1947-1967 (Folder 12)
  - Laverich, Henry P., 1953 (Folder 13)
  - Lawrence, David, 1953-56 (Folder 14)
  - Lazic, Zivota, 1969-1983 (Folder 15)
  - Lazitch, Branko, 1980 (Folder 16)
  - Lee, Luther J., 1943-46 (Folder 17)
  - Leiserson, Avery, 1952-1967 (Folder 18)
  - Leiserson, Michael, 1967 (Folder 19)
  - Lekic, Zivojin D., 1953 (Folder 20)
  - Leontief, Wassily, 1954 (Folder 21)
  - Levine, Edward M., 1981 (Folder 22)
  - Lewis, John D., 1957 (Folder 23)
  - Lieber, Charles D., 1957-1965 (Folder 24)
  - Life magazine, 1953 (Folder 25)
  - Lijphart, Arend, 1977-78 (Folder 26)
  - Linfield College, 1953-1977 (Folder 27)
  - Lippmann, Walter, 1946 (Folder 28)
  - Livingston, William S., 1977-79 (Folder 29)
  - Lodge, Henry Cabot, 1951 (Folder 30)
  - Loeb, William, 1958-59 (Folder 31)
  - London, Kurt L., 1965 (Folder 32)
  - Loomis, Henry, 1957 (Folder 33)
  - Luce, Clare Boothe, 1953 (Folder 34)
  - Lund, Mrs. Russell T., 1956-57 (Folder 35)
  - Luthi, Jack, 1956 (Folder 36)
  - McAlpin, Ruth D., 1956 (Folder 37)
  - MacArthur Foundation, 1982 (Folder 38)
  - McArthur, Robert E., 1975 (Folder 39)
  - McBrayer, James D., 1964-66 (Folder 40)
  - McCaffree, Floyd E., 1945 (Folder 41)
  - McCanless, Sarah, 1953-53 (Folder 42)
  - McCarran, Pat, 1951 (Folder 43)
  - McClellan, Woodford, 1969 (Folder 44)
  - McClosky, Herbert, 1955 (Folder 45)
  - McConnell Foundation, 1975 (Folder 46)
  - McCormick, John, 1955 (Folder 47)
  - McCreery, H. F., 1981 (Folder 48)
  - McDonald, Timothy G., 1955 (Folder 49)
  - McDowell, Robert H., 1968-1970 (Folder 50)
  - McFadden, H. H., 1950-51 (Folder 51)
  - McGonigal, Virginia, 1949 (Folder 52)
  - McGraw-Hill Book Company, 1958-59 (Folder 53)
  - MacInness, Donald, 1946-1987 (Folder 54)
  - McKean, Dayton, 1954 (Folder 55)
  - McKee, Wilbur R., 1962 (Folder 56)
  - MacKenzie, David, 1975-1987 (Folder 57)
  - McKenzie, R. T., 1957 (Folder 58)
  - MacKnight, Jesse, 1945-1965 (Folder 59)
  - McLean, Donald, 1951 (Folder 60)
  - McLean, E. Lee, 1969 (Folder 61)
  - MacLean, Fitzroy, 1957 (Folder 62)
  - MacMillan Company, 1953 (Folder 63)
  - Macridis, Roy C., 1951-1980 (Folder 64)
  - Madjerek, Z., 1950-51 (Folder 65)
  - Magner, Thomas, 1956-58 (Folder 66)
  - Maksimovic, Stevo, 1963 (Folder 67)
  - Mamchur, Steven, 1946 (Folder 68)
  - Manfred, Ernest, 1954-55 (Folder 69)
  - Mann, Ann, 1979 (Folder 70)
  - Mansfield, Harvey, 1950-1963 (Folder 71)
  - Marcovitch, Lazare, 1954-55 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Marcy, Oliver M., 1953 (Folder 2)
  - Marich, John T., 1955 (Folder 3)
  - Markovic, M. A., 1980 (Folder 4)
  - Markovic, Mihailo, 1963-1976 (Folder 5)
  - Martin, Joseph W., 1954 (Folder 6)
  - Mason, David, 1986 (Folder 7)
  - Mason, John Brown, 1960-61 (Folder 8)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, 1949-1955 (Folder 9)
  - Matlock, Jack F., 1987-88 (Folder 10)
  - Maxwell Air Force Base, 1953-54 (Folder 11)
  - May, Benjamin M., 1961-62 (Folder 12)
  - Mayada, Jaro, 1953 (Folder 13)
  - Mayer, Philip, 1955 (Folder 14)
  - Mayhew, Christopher, 1951 (Folder 15)
  - Maynard, Robert P., n.d. (Folder 16)
  - Maysles, Albert, 1956 (Folder 17)
  - Medvedev, Zhores, 1977 (Folder 18)
  - Meese, Edwin, 1982 (Folder 19)
  - "Meet the Press," 1954 (Folder 20)
  - Melich, Mitchell, 1972 (Folder 21)
  - Merchant, Livingston T., 1953 (Folder 22)
  - Mestrovic, Mate, 1979 (Folder 23)
  - Meyerowitz, Ira, 1954 (Folder 24)
  - Mickiewicz, Ellen, 1984 (Folder 25)
  - Micocci, Antonio A., 1948-1955 (Folder 26)
  - Mid-European Studies Center, 1953 (Folder 27)
  - Mihailovich, Vasa, 1976-79 (Folder 28)
  - Mihajlovich, Dusan, 1964 (Folder 29)
  - Mihelich, Anton, 1957 (Folder 30)
  - Mikasinovich, Branislav, 1967 (Folder 31)
  - Mikesell, Phillip, 1972 (Folder 32)
  - Milan, Shijachki, 1975 (Folder 33)
  - Milenkovitch, Michael, 1973-77 (Folder 34)
  - Milisavljevic, Dusan, 1954 (Folder 35)
  - Miller, Cleo M., 1954 (Folder 36)
  - Mills, Lennox, 1942-46 (Folder 37)
  - Milne, R. S., 1966 (Folder 38)
  - Milojkovic-Djuric, Jelena, 1987-88 (Folder 39)
  - Milosevic, Mihailo, 1966 (Folder 40)
  - Miskovic, D., 1984 (Folder 41)
  - Miskovic, Gordana, 1980 (Folder 42)
  - Modercin, Ivan, 1946 (Folder 43)
  - Modern Encyclopedia of Russian and Soviet History, 1979 (Folder 44)
  - Modini, Evelyn, 1967-69 (Folder 45)
  - Montana State University, 1964-65 (Folder 46)
  - Moody, Blair, 1951 (Folder 47)
  - Mooradian, Tom, 1956 (Folder 48)
  - Moore, Barrington, 1950-51 (Folder 49)
  - Moore, Wilbert E., 1943-1965 (Folder 50)
  - Moos, Malcolm, 1967 (Folder 51)
  - Moran, Theodore H., 1972-77 (Folder 52)
  - Morin, Alexander, 1953 (Folder 53)
  - Morley, Charles, 1957 (Folder 54)
  - Morrison, John, 1946 (Folder 55)
  - Morse, Wayne, 1951 (Folder 56)
  - Mosely, Philip E., 1955-58 (Folder 57)
  - Mount, William M., 1957 (Folder 58)
  - Moyers, Bill, 1963 (Folder 59)
  - Mrkela, Marko G., 1971 (Folder 60)
  - Mudd, Clayton, 1955 (Folder 61)
  - Munjic, Dimitrije, 1959-1980 (Folder 62)
  - Nasa Rec, 1984-87 (Folder 63)
  - Nashville Banner, 1956, 1974 (Folder 64)
  - Nashville Business and Professional Women's Club, 1950 (Folder 65)
  - Nashville Committee on Foreign Affairs, 1956-57 (Folder 66)
  - National Archives, 1980 (Folder 67)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities, 1986 (Folder 68)
  - National Interest, 1987 (Folder 69)
  - National Review, 1987 (Folder 70)
  - National War College, 1961 (Folder 71)
  - Naval War College (Box 11)
    - 1958 (Folder 1)
    - 1958-1962 (Folder 2)
  - Neal, Fred Warner, 1955-1963 (Folder 3)
  - Neal, Martha, 1974 (Folder 4)
  - Nelson, Pat, 1958 (Folder 5)
  - Nelson's Encyclopedia, 1946-47 (Folder 6)
  - Nemzer, Louis, 1946-1965 (Folder 7)
  - New Leader (NY), 1958 (Folder 8)
  - New Republic, 1985 (Folder 9)
  - New York Times, 1953-1988 (Folder 10)
  - Newstead, Hugh W., 1950 (Folder 11)
  - Newsweek, 1972-73 (Folder 12)
  - Nichols, William I., 1951 (Folder 13)
  - Niciforovic, Stevan, 1975-76 (Folder 14)
  - Nikiforow, Charles M., 1957 (Folder 15)
  - Nikitovich, Chaslav, 1969-1978 (Folder 16)
  - Nikolin, William, 1954-1973 (Folder 17)
  - Nimmo, Dan, 1963-64 (Folder 18)
  - Nixon, Richard M., 1968 (Folder 19)
  - "Njegos" Serbian Historical and Cultural Society, 1970-77 (Folder 20)
  - Noble, Osee, 1954 (Folder 21)
  - North American Society for Serbian Studies, 1978-1987 (Folder 22)
  - North Carolina State University, 1970-79 (Folder 23)
  - North Coast Institute, 1981 (Folder 24)
  - Obradovic, Joe, 1988 (Folder 25)
  - Obradovich, Maria, 1949-1951 (Folder 26)
  - Ocokoljich, F., 1954 (Folder 27)
  - O'Connor, Lucile, 1987 (Folder 28)
  - Ogden, Daniel M., 1959, 1964 (Folder 29)
  - Ogg, Frederic, 1945-46 (Folder 30)
  - Ogle, M. Bladen, 1945-49 (Folder 31)
  - O'Lee, Corinne, 1964 (Folder 32)
  - Oller, Thomas, 1987 (Folder 33)
  - Oman, William M., 1951 (Folder 34)
  - Owings, W. A., 1975-1980 (Folder 35)
  - Oxford University Press, 1953 (Folder 36)
  - Oyugi, Walter, 1987 (Folder 37)
  - Ozerovic, Aleksandar, 1957 (Folder 38)
  - Packwood, Bob, 1984 (Folder 39)
  - Padgett, Deborah, 1984 (Folder 40)
  - Pagac, Benedict, 1959 (Folder 41)
  - Palmer, Mark, 1985 (Folder 42)
  - Palmer, Robert C., 1960 (Folder 43)
  - Palms, John M., 1979-1980 (Folder 44)
  - Pantich, Tihomir, 1984 (Folder 45)
  - Parezanin, Ratko, 1953 (Folder 46)
  - Paris, Edmond, 1962 (Folder 47)
  - Parks, Norman L., 1952 (Folder 48)
  - Parrent, Allan M., 1961 (Folder 49)
  - Parrish, W. R., 1953 (Folder 50)
  - Parthemos, George S., 1958-1965 (Folder 51)
  - Partridge, Richard, 1953 (Folder 52)
  - Pasic, Nicholas, 1969-1979 (Folder 53)
  - Paulson, Eleanor, 1953-1970 (Folder 54)
  - Pavelic, A. Smith, 1953-58 (Folder 55)
  - Pavlovich, Paul P., 1981-88 (Folder 56)
  - Pavlowitch, Stevan K., 1973-76 (Folder 57)
  - Payne, Thomas, 1959-1981 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Pazarac, Pavle V., 1956 (Folder 2)
  - Pearson, Drew, 1964 (Folder 3)
  - Pejovich, Steve, 1981 (Folder 4)
  - Pekovich, Waso, 1959 (Folder 5)
  - Pellman, Marjorie, 1959 (Folder 6)
  - Pempel, T. J., 1980 (Folder 7)
  - Penniman, Howar, 1954 (Folder 8)
  - Perdue, James E., 1961 (Folder 9)
  - Perry, Richard A., 1972 (Folder 10)
  - Petkovic, Sava, 1950-51 (Folder 11)
  - Petkovich, Dusan, 1977 (Folder 12)
  - Petrovich, Michael B., 1949-1987 (Folder 13)
  - Phelps, Edwin P., 1955 (Folder 14)
  - Phoenix Gazette, 1957 (Folder 15)
  - Piekalkiewicz, Jaroslaw, 1973 (Folder 16)
  - Pietrow, John, 1966 (Folder 17)
  - Pikl, I. James, 1953 (Folder 18)
  - Pipes, Richard, 1984 (Folder 19)
  - Pirocanac, Steve, 1987-88 (Folder 20)
  - Pletnev, Rostislav, 1966 (Folder 21)
  - Plischke, Elmer, 1967 (Folder 22)
  - Polich, Todor, 1970 (Folder 23)
  - Pollock, James K., 1946 (Folder 24)
  - Polsby, Nelson W., 1986 (Folder 25)
  - Poole, Dewitt C., 1944-1952 (Folder 26)
  - Popovich, Dragan, 1954 (Folder 27)
  - Portis, Edward B., 1975 (Folder 28)
  - Pounds, N. J. G., 1955-56 (Folder 29)
  - Praeger, Frederick, 1957 (Folder 30)
  - Pranger, Robert J., 1964-68 (Folder 31)
  - Prentice-Hall, Inc., 1947-1955 (Folder 32)
  - Prescott, Frank W., 1962 (Folder 33)
  - Pribic, Nikola, 1975-1986 (Folder 34)
  - Price, Don K., 1960 (Folder 35)
  - Priest, J. Percy, 1953 (Folder 36)
  - Prometheus Books, 1981 (Folder 37)
  - Public Affairs Press, 1961 (Folder 38)
  - Puhan, Alfred, 1950 (Folder 39)
  - Puric, G., 1970-74 (Folder 40)
  - Radan, Peter, 1988 (Folder 41)
  - Radin, George, 1968-1976 (Folder 42)
  - Raditsa, Bogdan, 1954 (Folder 43)
  - Radojevich, Djuro, 1970 (Folder 44)
  - Radojevich, George, 1979 (Folder 45)
  - Radosavljevich, Milka, 1985 (Folder 46)
  - Radovich, Milan, 1980 (Folder 47)
  - Rajic, Milan L., 1966, 1972-77 (Folder 48)
  - Rakic, Milovan, 1988 (Folder 49)
  - Rakowska-Harmstone, Teresa, 1979 (Folder 50)
  - Ramee, Stephen, 1975 (Folder 51)
  - Ramet, Pedro, 1988 (Folder 52)
  - Ramsaur, Ernest E., 1949 (Folder 53)
  - Ramsdell, Edward T., 1954 (Folder 54)
  - Rand McNally and Company, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Random House Publishers, 1953-1980 (Folder 2)
  - Rankovich Fund, 1981 (Folder 3)
  - Ranney, Austin, 1974-78 (Folder 4)
  - Ransom, H. H., 1965 (Folder 5)
  - Rasmussen, Jorgen, 1969-1978 (Folder 6)
  - Reams, Elinor, 1949-1950 (Folder 7)
  - Reams, R. Borden, 1953, 1976-77 (Folder 8)
  - Redford, Emmette, 1954 (Folder 9)
  - Relm Foundation, 1959-1966 (Folder 10)
  - Remington, Thomas F., 1988 (Folder 11)
  - The Reporter (NY), 1955 (Folder 12)
  - Republic Library, n.d. (Folder 13)
  - Reshetar, John S., 1972-78 (Folder 14)
  - Revey, E. Lewis, 1949-1957 (Folder 15)
  - Rhodes, Don, 1988 (Folder 16)
  - Rice, Maurice S., 1948 (Folder 17)
  - Rice, Ross R., 1962 (Folder 18)
  - Riethmayer, Leo C., 1954-55 (Folder 19)
  - Riggs, Fred W., 1961 (Folder 20)
  - Roberts, Henry L., 1957 (Folder 21)
  - Roberts, Walter R., 1957, 1971-74 (Folder 22)
  - Robinson, Geroid, 1945 (Folder 23)
  - Roett, Riordan, 1969-1978 (Folder 24)
  - Rosenberg, George, 1947 (Folder 25)
  - Ross, Ralph G., 1957 (Folder 26)
  - Ross, Rochelle, 1979 (Folder 27)
  - Rossinoff, Barry, 1976 (Folder 28)
  - Rothman, Stanley, 1960-61 (Folder 29)
  - Rothschild, Joseph, 1957 (Folder 30)
  - Roucek, Joseph, 1955-1970 (Folder 31)
  - Ruggles, Melville, 1950-57 (Folder 32)
  - Ruppel, Louis, 1951 (Folder 33)
  - Russell, Frank M., 1942-1954 (Folder 34)
  - Rustin, John W., 1956 (Folder 35)
  - Rutgers University Press, 1980-81 (Folder 36)
  - Ryavec, Karl, 1980 (Folder 37)
  - St. John, George, 1951 (Folder 38)
  - St. Sava Serbian Orthodox Church (Gary, Indiana), 1976-77 (Folder 39)
  - Salatich, William G., 1986 (Folder 40)
  - San Jose Mercury News, 1978 (Folder 41)
  - Sanders, Irwin T., 1959 (Folder 42)
  - Sanders, Marion, 1951 (Folder 43)
  - Sandlin, Cleo W., 1955 (Folder 44)
  - Sapin, Burton, 1955-1970 (Folder 45)
  - Sargeant, Howland, 1952-56 (Folder 46)
  - Saslaw, Joseph, 1949-1956 (Folder 47)
  - Sasser, Jim, 1953-1988 (Folder 48)
  - Saunders, Allan F., 1954 (Folder 49)
  - Savich, Jovan D., 1988 (Folder 50)
  - Scantland, Harriett, 1947 (Folder 51)
  - Scepanovich, R., 1980 (Folder 52)
  - Scheuer, Steven, 1960 (Folder 53)
  - Schindler, Oswald, 1949 (Folder 54)
  - Schlesinger, Arthur, 1960 (Folder 55)
  - Schratz, Paul R., 1960-1971 (Folder 56)
  - Schroeder, Gertrude, 1981 (Folder 57)
  - Schuman, Frederick, 1953-55 (Folder 58)
  - Schwarcz, John, 1973 (Folder 59)
  - Scribners' Sons Publishers, 1961 (Folder 60)
  - Seffer, Urosh, 1955-1971 (Folder 61)
  - Semrau, Gay, 1988 (Folder 62)
  - Serb World (Milwaukee), 1980 (Folder 63)
  - Serb World USA (Tucson), 1985 (Folder 64)
  - Serbian Heritage Books, 1985 (Folder 65)
  - Serbian Historical and Cultural Society "Njegos," 1980 (Folder 66)
  - Serbian National Committee, 1978-1980 (Folder 67)
  - Serbian National Defense Council of America, 1955-1965 (Folder 68)
  - Serbian National Shield Society of Canada, 1987 (Folder 69)
  - Seton-Watson, Hugh, 1977-79 (Folder 70)
  - Shelah, Menachem, 1987 (Folder 71)
  - Shepherd, Philip, 1979 (Folder 72)
  - Sherwood, Foster H., 1961 (Folder 73)
  - Shipley, R. B., 1954 (Folder 74)
  - Shockley, Barbara, 1953 (Folder 75)
  - Short, Samuel J., 1980 (Folder 76)
  - Shoup, Earl L., 1948-1950 (Folder 77)
  - Shugg, Roger W., 1955-57 (Folder 78)
  - Shulman, Marshall, 1961-62 (Folder 79)
  - Sills, Joe B., 1958-1977 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Simich, Obrad, 1953 (Folder 2)
  - Simidjioski, Slobodan, 1962 (Folder 3)
  - Simpson, Ruth, 1952 (Folder 4)
  - Sjeklocha, Paul, 1970 (Folder 5)
  - Skrivanic, Gavro, 1980 (Folder 6)
  - Skoric, Sofija, 1974-1988 (Folder 7)
  - Slaughter, D. French, 1985 (Folder 8)
  - Slavic Review, 1982-84 (Folder 9)
  - Slijepcevic, Djoko, 1975 (Folder 10)
  - Sloan, John, 1987 (Folder 11)
  - Smith College, 1960 (Folder 12)
  - Smith, J. J., 1957 (Folder 13)
  - Smith, Lawrence H., 1953 (Folder 14)
  - Social Science Research Council, 1951-58 (Folder 15)
  - Society of Serbian Writers and Artists Abroad, 1979-1987 (Folder 16)
  - Somit, Albert, 1961-1980 (Folder 17)
  - Sommer, Richard L., 1961 (Folder 18)
  - Soni, Parma, 1954 (Folder 19)
  - Soubbotitch, Ivan, 1970-73 (Folder 20)
  - South Slav Journal (London), 1986-87 (Folder 21)
  - Speier, Mary P., 1953 (Folder 22)
  - Spellacy, E. F., 1954 (Folder 23)
  - Spencer, Charles, 1963-1971 (Folder 24)
  - Spofford, Dorothy, 1955-56 (Folder 25)
  - Sproul, Robert, 1942 (Folder 26)
  - Staar, Richard F., 1957-1975 (Folder 27)
  - Stahl, Walter, 1957 (Folder 28)
  - Stambaugh, John H., 1972-1980 (Folder 29)
  - Stanisic, Branislav, 1972 (Folder 30)
  - Stankovich, Urosh, 1976 (Folder 31)
  - Stefan, Charles G., 1956-1981 (Folder 32)
  - Steiger, Donald, 1975 (Folder 33)
  - Stein, Harold, 1953-54 (Folder 34)
  - Steiner, H. Arthur, 1957 (Folder 35)
  - Stephenson, Jay, 1951-55 (Folder 36)
  - Stetson, Dorothy M., 1975 (Folder 37)
  - Stevenson, Adlai, 1953 (Folder 38)
  - Stillman, Edmund O., 1948 (Folder 39)
  - Stojanovic, Svetozar, 1975-79 (Folder 40)
  - Stokes, Gale, 1970-76 (Folder 41)
  - Stone, Albert W., 1964 (Folder 42)
  - Strausz-Hupe, Robert, 1956 (Folder 43)
  - Strelsky, Nikander, 1959 (Folder 44)
  - Strmecki, Joseph, 1954 (Folder 45)
  - Stumpf, Samuel, 1967 (Folder 46)
  - Sujdovic, M. Mike, 1986 (Folder 47)
  - Sullivan, Walter, 1988 (Folder 48)
  - Sulzberger, C. L., 1950-1985 (Folder 49)
  - Surber, Bill, 1957 (Folder 50)
  - Symposium Life of Contrast, 1981 (Folder 51)
  - Taborsky, Edward, 1958-1962 (Folder 52)
  - Talbot, Phillips, 1954 (Folder 53)
  - Talhami, Soulofa, 1981 (Folder 54)
  - Tamkoc, Metin, 1963-64 (Folder 55)
  - Tanaskovich, Dushan, 1951-56 (Folder 56)
  - Tanenhaus, Joseph, 1958-1972 (Folder 57)
  - Tanmore, Dean, 1959 (Folder 58)
  - Taylor, A. J. P., 1958 (Folder 59)
  - Taylor, Brown, 1961 (Folder 60)
  - Taylor, Tillman, 1957 (Folder 61)
  - Tennessee Polytechnic Institute, 1957 (Folder 62)
  - Tennessee State University, 1975-76 (Folder 63)
  - Tennyson, Charles L., 1959 (Folder 64)
  - Thatcher, Max, 1946-1955 (Folder 65)
  - Theen, Rolf, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Thompson, Alan R., 1974 (Folder 2)
  - Thompson, Charles, 1981 (Folder 3)
  - Thompson, E. Bigelow, 1948 (Folder 4)
  - Thompson, Kenneth W., 1959-1961 (Folder 5)
  - Thornton, James J., 1952 (Folder 6)
  - Thorogood, James, 1957 (Folder 7)
  - Thurber, Clarence, 1957 (Folder 8)
  - Tochitch, Desimir, 1969-1980 (Folder 9)
  - Todorovic, Slavko, 1951-1976 (Folder 10)
  - Todorovic, Stephen J., 1953 (Folder 11)
  - Toma, Peter, 1972 (Folder 12)
  - Tomasevich, Jozo, 1948-1970 (Folder 13)
  - Tomashevich, George V., 1983-87 (Folder 14)
  - Tomasic, Dinko A., 1952 (Folder 15)
  - Tosic, Desimir, 1979 (Folder 16)
  - Towster, Julian, 1945-1963 (Folder 17)
  - Trickovich, Richard, 1975 (Folder 18)
  - Trifkovic, B., 1980 (Folder 19)
  - Trivunac, Stevan, 1961-1970 (Folder 20)
  - Tsurutani, Taketsugu, 1981 (Folder 21)
  - Tuttle, Robert H., 1988 (Folder 22)
  - Twentieth Century Fund, 1960 (Folder 23)
  - Twombly, Jack, 1949-1950 (Folder 24)
  - Tyirin, William, 1971 (Folder 25)
  - Tyler, William, 1949 (Folder 26)
  - United Nations Association of the U.S.A., 1980 (Folder 27)
  - U.S. Capitol Historical Society, 1986-88 (Folder 28)
  - U.S. Department of State, 1947-1986 (Folder 29)
  - U.S. Environmental Protection Agency, 1981 (Folder 30)
  - U.S. Information Agency, 1956-57 (Folder 31)
  - U.S. News and World Report, 1956 (Folder 32)
  - U.S. Office of Personnel Management, 1986 (Folder 33)
  - United States Quarterly Book Review, 1950 (Folder 34)
  - University of Alberta (Calgary), 1964-65 (Folder 35)
  - University of Arizona, 1978 (Folder 36)
  - University of California
    - Berkeley, 1942 (Folder 37)
    - Berkeley Library, 1950 (Folder 38)
    - Santa Barbara, 1979-1981 (Folder 39)
  - University of Illinois (Chicago), 1977 (Folder 40)
  - University of Kentucky Press, 1952 (Folder 41)
  - University of Michigan (Ann Arbor), 1946 (Folder 42)
  - University of Missouri (Kansas City), 1972 (Folder 43)
  - University of Montana (Missoula), 1965 (Folder 44)
  - University of Tennessee (Nashville), 1975 (Folder 45)
  - University of Utah (Salt Lake City), 1947 (Folder 46)
  - University of Virginia (Charlottesville), 1973-1987 (Folder 47)
  - University of Wyoming (Laramie), 1964 (Folder 48)
  - Usenik, Frances, 1949-1955 (Folder 49)
  - Vanderbilt University
    - 1959-1977 (Folder 50)
    - 1978-1981 (Folder 51)
  - Van Horn, Eleanor, 1943-45 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Van Meter, George, 1958 (Folder 2)
  - Vassar Political Association, 1956 (Folder 3)
  - Vaurs, Roger, 1953 (Folder 4)
  - Vernon, Manfred, 1958-1966 (Folder 5)
  - Vlahovic, V. S., 1953 (Folder 6)
  - Voegeli, Jacque, 1980 (Folder 7)
  - Voice of Canadian Serbs, 1985 (Folder 8)
  - Volgyes, Ivan, 1986 (Folder 9)
  - Vosnjak, Bogumil, 1954 (Folder 10)
  - Vranesh, Lola, 1973-78 (Folder 11)
  - Vuchic, Vukan, 1961-67 (Folder 12)
  - Vucinich, Alexander, 1946 (Folder 13)
  - Vucinich, Wayne S., 1943-1987 (Folder 14)
  - Vuckovic, Zvonimir, 1987 (Folder 15)
  - Vukasin, Peter N., 1953 (Folder 16)
  - Vukcevich, Ivo, 1979 (Folder 17)
  - Vukcevich, Radoje, 1962-69 (Folder 18)
  - Vukovic, L., 1976-1984 (Folder 19)
  - Vukovic-Bircanin, N., 1978 (Folder 20)
  - Vuksanovic, Vladeta, 1970-72 (Folder 21)
  - Wahlke, John, 1957-1970 (Folder 22)
  - Waldron, Ellis, 1965 (Folder 23)
  - Walker, Peter, 1957-58 (Folder 24)
  - Walkin, Jacob, 1953-1983 (Folder 25)
  - Waller, Derek, 1969-1973 (Folder 26)
  - Ward, Ray, 1959-1961 (Folder 27)
  - Ward, Robert E., 1954 (Folder 28)
  - Ware, Richard A., 1959 (Folder 29)
  - Warner, John W., 1984-88 (Folder 30)
  - Washington Post, 1978-1987 (Folder 31)
  - Washington Quarterly, 1988 (Folder 32)
  - Watkins, Arthur V., 1954 (Folder 33)
  - Watkins, Robert L., 1980 (Folder 34)
  - Weaver, Ellsworth, 1961 (Folder 35)
  - Weaver, Herbert, 1956-1984 (Folder 36)
  - Webb, Kenneth C., 1946 (Folder 37)
  - Weeks, Edward, 1951 (Folder 38)
  - Weidner, Edward, 1957 (Folder 39)
  - Weiner, E. J., 1953 (Folder 40)
  - Weiner, Myron, 1971 (Folder 41)
  - Weintraub, Stanley, 1986 (Folder 42)
  - Welsh, Jerry, 1969 (Folder 43)
  - Welsh, William, 1984 (Folder 44)
  - Western Reserve University, 1945-1964 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Western Washington State College, 1964 (Folder 2)
  - Westerners International, 1972 (Folder 3)
  - White, Charles H., 1952 (Folder 4)
  - White, Wilbur W., 1948-49 (Folder 5)
  - Whitney, Mary, 1988 (Folder 6)
  - Wickstead, George, 1981 (Folder 7)
  - Widmayer, Ruth, 1956-1965 (Folder 8)
  - Wieczynski, Joseph, 1979-1980 (Folder 9)
  - Wilbens, Laura, 1967 (Folder 10)
  - Wilborough, Jean, 1977 (Folder 11)
  - Wilcox, Francis O., 1946-1961 (Folder 12)
  - Wilcox, Stanley, 1952-57 (Folder 13)
  - Wilder, Oren, 1954 (Folder 14)
  - Wiley, Alexander, 1953 (Folder 15)
  - Wiley, Richard, 1975 (Folder 16)
  - Wiley and Sons, Inc., 1957 (Folder 17)
  - Willen, Paul, 1954 (Folder 18)
  - Williams, G. Mennen, 1957-1973 (Folder 19)
  - Williams, Henry N., 1957 (Folder 20)
  - Williams, J. D., 1966 (Folder 21)
  - Williams, Peggy, n.d. (Folder 22)
  - Williamson, Samuel R., 1987 (Folder 23)
  - Wilson, David K., 1980 (Folder 24)
  - Woinovich, Ilija, 1952 (Folder 25)
  - Wolff, Robert Lee, 1948-1955 (Folder 26)
  - Wolin, Sheldon, 1964 (Folder 27)
  - Woodell, Marshall, 1977 (Folder 28)
  - World Affairs Interpreter, 1949 (Folder 29)
  - Wright, Quincy, 1947 (Folder 30)
  - Younger, Ed, 1962 (Folder 31)
  - Yugoslav Anticommunist Committee, 1959 (Folder 32)
  - Yugoslav Press and Cultural Center, New York, 1980 (Folder 33)
  - Zacek, Joseph, 1975 (Folder 34)
  - Zecevic, Dragana, 1978-1981 (Folder 35)
  - Zekulin, Gleb, 1981 (Folder 36)
  - Zeldin, Jesse, 1981 (Folder 37)
  - Zenkovsky, Serge, 1976 (Folder 38)
  - Zivkovich, Branko S., 1949-1951 (Folder 39)
  - Zukov, Mary, 1951 (Folder 40)
  - Miscellaneous (Folder 41-43)
- Speeches and Writings, 1938-1990 (Boxes 17-22)
  Drafts, manuscript copies, printed copies, reports, speech transcripts, clippings, notes and sources materials, correspondence and other miscellany. Arranged chronologically.
  - General
    - Correspondence relating to speeches and writings
      - General (Box 17, Folder 44)
      - Dorsey Press, 1976-78 (Folder 45)
      - Rutgers University Press
        - 1955-1973 (Folder 46)
        - 1973-77 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Drafts and notes (Folder 2-3)
  - "The Challenge We Face," n.d. Holograph. (Folder 4)
  - "The Development of Parliamentary Government in Serbia," n.d. Typescript. (Folder 5-6)
  - "French Politics," n.d. Holograph. (Folder 7)